KATELYN MICHALOVE

Product Designer

katelynmichalove@gmail.com katelynmichalove.com

615-613-5617

EXPERIENCE

Sunbelt Rentals / Product Designer

July 2019 - present Remote

• Sunbeltrentals.com - authenticated space

Design lead for the complete redesign of Sunbelt's primary digital touch point with the goal of increasing overall usage from 21% to 100%. As a part of this effort, I conducted stakeholder interviews, user interviews, launched a customer survey, and took designs from wireframes to launch.

• Dispatch and Logistics Platform

Product redesign to indentify inefficiencies and increase transportation profitability. This involved field interviews and observations, wireframing new solutions and features to solve dispatcher needs, utilizing and contributing to a design system, usability testing and iteration.

SmartEquip - iOS Mobile Inspection Application
1 Week sprint redesign to improve the user flows, match iOS
HIG, and convert visual design to Sunbelt branding guidelines.

Solve usability issues discovered in field pilot testing.

Freelance / Product Designer

August 2018- July 2019 Remote

• Baseball analytics website to help launch a new business.

Procter and Gamble / Process Engineer

June 2017 - July 2018 Sacramento, CA

• Led troubleshooting for the chemical plant to solve for process improvement areas.

EDUCATION

University of Tennessee / 2017 / BA Chemical Engineering

Bloc / 2019 / UX Design Apprenticeship

SUMMARY

I am a Product Designer with skills in conducting user research, leading projects, wireframing, visual design, and using and contributing to design systems. I've collaborated with executives, outside design vendors, end users, developers and internal teams. My goal is to solve for user needs while balancing and meeting business objectives.

TOOLS

Sketch, Figma

Marvel, Invision

Adobe Creative Suite

Dovetail

Lookback

Miro

Survey Gizmo

Git, GitHub

Google Analytics

HTML, CSS

Jira

SKILL SET

UX/UI Design

Visual Design

User Research

Market Research

Usability Testing

Information Architecture

Branding

Prototyping

Frontend Development